Friends, it is said that when a person is going through
bad times, when the situation becomes bad, then
his own relatives, friends,
friends, all leave him.
Whenever he [Sangeet] needs money in bad times, no
one comes forward to help.
But in these bad times, there are some
banks and some NBFC companies [music]
that come forward to help you.
Gives you a loan [music].  But they also
give you loan only when your internal
conditions are good.  By internal conditions I
mean that when your CIBIL score is good
[music] only then companies, NBFCs,
banks give you loans.   So,
when she gives a loan,
innocent people take help from her once.
But how do they cheat you after giving the loan or in the name of giving the loan
[music]?
You have never done this.  I would never have thought about the meaning.  Till date you might
not have noticed that she
also cheats you.  Today I will tell you how she cheats.
So hello [music] friends,
my name is Sunil and today I am going to expose one such
NBFC company, Non Banking Financial
Company and
you must have heard its name many times on Instagram, YouTube
or Facebook [music] or must have
seen some of their ads.  So before I expose them
[music] please like my video
, share it, and do
n't forget to comment.
Subscribing is most important.  Please do that.
This gives me encouragement.
So that company is none other than
Money View Company.
I had taken a loan of Rs 5 lakh from Money View Company on 4 January 2024.
He gave me a loan.  Ok.
I took that money and used it.  But along with
that loan they gave me an
ICI Lombard policy.  Meaning, the
purpose of taking that policy was this [music] or
their purpose of selling the policy is that in
case, during the period of
loan being in force,
something happens to the customer in whose name the
loan is running, then the entire amount will be given
to the insurance company.  So similarly Money
View Company gave me an ICI Lombard
insurance along with it for something like Rs 10,500.
I took it just because I thought that
if anything happens to me in these three
years, then I mean, this ICC will pay for it.
So from 5th January 2024 till today
that policy has not been sent to me by Money View or ICI
Lombard.   I
mean, I also sent him a lot of emails.  I
tried to contact them a lot but
till date they have not sent me that policy.
Regarding this, I already have a dispute with him [Sangeet].  That
means
I have filed a case against them in the consumer court.
But still I thought
why not tell you about their evil deeds
through this video.   I should
expose them so that they do
not cheat you like they cheated me.
So what happened was that on 5th January 2000 [Music] Sorry
24 4th January 2024 when I took the loan,
they gave me the policy and I waited for 7 to 8
months whereas as per the IRDA
guidelines, that policy should
reach the customer within 15 days
through mail and within 30 days the hard copy should
reach his home by post.
But he did nothing.  Neither did she
send it to me by mail nor did I receive it at home.
So I waited for them three-four months ago thinking
that maybe they would send it, but they did not send it.
After that I sent him mails saying that I had
taken a loan from you like this.  Along with that you
gave me an ICI Lombard policy of something like Rs
10,500.  But there was no response from them.
Nothing [music] came.  Then
in October 2024, I put their
[music]
EMI on hold for a short period.  So
after holding, they [singing voice]
contacted me.  I started getting calls from these [music]
recovery agents.   She started
talking rudely to me.  [MUSIC]
But it continued like this.  I did
those pays [music] after a while.
Because at that time my situation became a little
worse, due to some reason my salary from my office [music] was
stopped.
Later I paid them.  But
even after that, he did not send me that policy
[music] till date.   Even
if I hold their policies [music], there is
no guarantee in their [song voice] ears that this
policy will be delivered to me on my mail [music] or at my
home.  So in the coming time,
I am seeing that the remaining one year
loan of theirs is about to be completed
[Music]
so after that,
I will again hold their EMI for the next one year.  But
in all these circumstances, no [music] is the biggest
bastard.  No one else does that bastardry.
That is done by Airtel and Jio.
How is that [music] that like
my number is registered in my [singing voice] name
with their money company, that
number is registered in my name.
Ok?  So what they do is that they collect data about
how many numbers are running in its name.  Whatever
number may be running.  One might be moving, two might be moving
, even [music] 10 might be moving.  They keep
calling everyone and saying that such and such
[sangeet] is not a person or Sunil Kumar
or anyone who had taken a loan is not paying it.  Get it done because the
guidelines of IRDA, RBI and Supreme Court [singing voice] are being violated.
From whose side?  From Money You Company.  And
who is doing the bastardry?  Airtel and Jio.
How are you doing this bastardry?  That
they have the biggest data of ours.  If we keep
giving our numbers to these companies.  So in
this way, they will give numbers to ISI also tomorrow [music].
ISI or Pakistan or any
enemy country will send the common man's Tata.
So this corruption is being done by Airtel and Jio
because I have
only these two numbers, one of Airtel and one of Jio, hence
I am taking their names only.  I am
not taking anyone's name much.  BSNL does
not have such networks.  Ok?  And let's just say this.
[MUSIC] The idea is just a
name.  So these guys stay away from them
[music].  She plays a huge fraud.
NBFC companies especially
like Money, there are many other such big companies
which I will keep exposing in the coming time,
one by one, two by two, but
whatever will be the matter about them [Music]
you will get the name of any company, any bank or any
credit card company,
I will announce it [Music] every Monday.
Whatever happens after that will be seen.
[Music] By the way, if you
enjoyed my video, don't forget to like, share, comment,
and most importantly, do
n't forget to subscribe [Music].
Thank you.  I am your friend Sunil Kumar.   I
need your permission [music].  Thank you.